The weather forecast has been really off lately.
So much for only a 10% chance of rain.
Hey, are you okay?
Oh, good. You're not hurt?
That's not that good.
Please, don't come any closer to me.
Don't hurt me.
Please, please don't hurt me.
The rain comes from an unknown world, washing the Earth with its tears.
Is this new meeting a temporary necessity, or is it more likely to be a contrived coincidence?
Because, as we all know, there is more than one truth.
Don't hurt me.
Okay.
See you next time.
I want people who are you to love
I have drawn out
cooking class and the other students taught me how so do you want to try one uh sure i'd love to
thanks hey tobichi no way you get out be careful shino that witch is going to do more damage i'm
so sorry although i know an apology is hardly enough why is this super genius apologizing to
him what are we missing maybe he's got some dirt on her that's so lame oh it's fine you can stop
bowing now just don't worry about it okay listen up no more cheating okay get your stinky hands off him
the report said that you stayed tell me what you're still doing here that's none of your business
now focus shido forget about the stupid ugly witch and eat my cookies and mine i baked cookies too
you need to stop copying me actually i baked mine first so you're copying me
wrong and besides look at your dumb cookies i bet they suck
yeah they're not all that great so here eat quick before she tries to make you eat her junk
no you should try mine first
yum they're both good mine must be better he ate it much faster incorrect he ate mine
one point two seconds faster than yours excuse me hey some strange little stranger just gave me
a whole bag of cookies do you want one cheeto i'd let her but she's watching her figure
man it wasn't supposed to rain today either
hey kotari i made it home i'm gonna go take a shower
get out of here right now kotari what's going on why is toka here hey welcome back home bro oh thanks
don't change the subject now please tell me what toka's doing in our house well i've decided she
should live with us you know at least for the time being okay do you mind telling me why that is
we have a good reason for this chill reina what are you doing here oh sorry am i using too much sugar
again no well yes but i don't really care about that toka's aftercare that's right fortunately when
she kissed you her spirit power was immediately and effectively sealed and now there is an invisible
road what we call a path between the two of you okay but what's this thing about a seal i explained
that to you after it happened when you kissed toka after raising her mood points you in particular were
able to absorb her spirit powers and seal them so why is it i have that kind of power i'm not sure
i just got lucky and figured it out with katasker's help can i continue with my point now if the spirit's
mental condition becomes unstable there is a significant probability that the power seals inside you will
return back to her our research is conclusive toka's numbers are the most stable when she is near you
until the special housing unit for spirits is completed it would be best for everyone if she
stays here right whatever this isn't a bad thing consider it a part of your training you mean i wasn't
finished toka's powers are already sealed what else am i supposed to do did i say toka was the only spirit
around there are more out there a lot more in fact special designation disaster beings also known as
spirits they come in all shapes and sizes just like us we want you to continue speaking with them
shin we need you to become even better at dealing with women the world needs you to become even better
at dealing with women great no pressure at all but i still don't get why i have to live with toka
i apologize shito i knew it i shouldn't be here no you're fine i'm a jerk this weird is never gonna
end of course fine i'm on it why does she have to be so mean when she's in her commander mode
i'm normally the one to do this stuff but still sorry i'm so sorry i should have knocked
oh are you crazy someone was in a rush shame on shito you did that on purpose i told you this
was training didn't i you need to learn how to face any situation calm and collected
soka i'm sorry i didn't know you were in there it's fine i forgive you just hand that to me please
shito i got a bath already for you you can go ahead and wash up
nah i'm good you go instead oh and here you can use these if you want
kotri has never given up first dibs when i've got these she should know not to underestimate me i
shito itzuka haven't grown up in the same house as you without learning a thing or two
that's so nice but uh why don't you go ahead and use them thanks though
hey toka you're not taking a bath right now no i'm standing in this door maybe i was being too suspicious
oh
go figure there are spirits besides toka i wonder how many there are and will i be able to save them all
kotri i'm gonna kill you not my fault you're dumb oh crap
you can't just bump out of me like that you know
and another fail this is supposed to be my training
shito it's time for lunch
why are you here witch you're not welcome i was going to say the same thing can't we all just eat
together
what what is it stare all you want i'm not sharing excuse me what is that
the thing is this morning we bought our bentos from the same place i bumped into toka while she was
there liar you bought this 154 days ago at the discount store in front of the station for 15
80. you've been using the same container ever since this is not from the bento shop
and how exactly do you know this that's not really important don't leave me out of the
conversation like that it's rude now what are you two talking about hey cheeto my girlfriend wants
me to help her pick out clothes do you think a french maid is best shrine maiden nurse maybe
strip dude this is not the best time who cares if she's a mate or whatever else
made it is
your attention please this is not a drill there have been a precursor
signs of an independent spatial quake in this vicinity
okay
there is shelter immediately i repeat there have been a precursor resign
kids another quake alarm we have to evacuate immediately move it or lose it as they say
yeah you want me to leave her behind yes remember her powers have been sealed so she's the same
as a normal human being besides we can't afford for her stress levels to go up watching a fight might
trigger that that's true she know toga miss marisame why are you dawdling back there if you don't hurry
up and evacuate you're going to be in serious trouble in serious danger
miss okamine will you watch toka for me what of course i'll keep an eye on her
she don't hey toka i need to leave you here okay something just came up i have to go but i'll be right
back now it's dangerous i'll be fine i promise shito ituka come back here you too miss marisame where
do you think you're going hey you made it well for the aftermath anyway
it's smaller than usual this time i'd like to say this was a good sign but this is about average for
a hermit hermit the name of the spirit that's appeared this time she's known for being more
docile than the other spirits we've seen hold on i've seen this girl before where and when i met
her at the shrine two nights ago we were already tracking her by then but we saw no disruption of
her main spirit wave numbers at that time so it's the same as it was for toka the ast has arrived they
are commencing their attack
how can they fire on a little girl what she looks like doesn't matter to the ast she's trying to
run away what they're doing is wrong don't feel sorry for her shito that behavior will only make
you weak
kotri let's do it i want to go save that girl there you go that's so my big brother for you listen up
prepare for a type one capture right okay i think it's about time we go on another date
hermit has entered the building ast i want you to hold your positions until the target has moved
so you think hermit is really going to come here yes based on the analysis there's no doubt the ast
probably won't be able to make a move for a while don't tell me you're here to bully yoshinan too
oh the lucky letcher has returned for more hasn't he
shito hold on a sec
talk to me people name your choice come on it's gotta be two this one's straight out of a dating sim go with
two isn't that risky if you don't know the other person's personality seems one is our best bet
hermit rarely attacks humans i'm gonna have to go with option three
shito go with three are you sure about that come on don't you know someone who would talk like that
don't watch it excuse me i don't know what you mean i'm just a wandering vagabond
you're trying to make me laugh aren't you nobody talks like that seriously
well i'm glad you liked my joke
so my name's shito you are oh i'm sorry how embarrassing i can't believe i forgot to introduce
myself to you my name is yoshina and it cute and it cute
yeah sure it's cute so is that your name or is it the name of the puppet do you guys share a name
shito her happiness meter just went down dramatically what did you say to her what
nothing i swear i was just trying to find out why she only talks through ventriloquism
i do not know what you were talking about shito what is ventriloquism look we'll figure out the
cause of this later for now just work on making her happy again right yeah i get your point so yoshinan's
just yoshinan oh shito you're one of those people who jokes around a lot aren't you why did you come
here oh because well i know it's sudden but will will you go on a date with me a date
do you think it's really all that dangerous outside there's no telling how dangerous it is
but with a spatial quake it's not worth the risk seriously toka doesn't know about spatial quakes
maybe she's like a spoiled super rich girl that's so lame mizuka mine why do you think shito would
leave during such a dangerous time honestly i have no idea you don't
she wants to save him she's totally brave i want to be here when i grow up that's so lame
well i'm sure shito will be perfectly fine there's really nothing to worry about toka you'll see huh
permission to shoot not gonna happen for a while we're talking about a weak little hermit here she
hasn't been that much of a threat yet nothing worth city damage and a call for support troops the
conditions with her are different than those with princess i still can't get over it a girl looking
just like princess transfers into your class without any spirit reactions detected there's seemingly nothing
wrong with her family register either i keep racking my brain trying to figure it out but to
tell you the truth i got nothing tell me what you think am i cool or am i the coolest ever hey wait
that's not safe hey wait i asked if i was cool or the coolest
that that was uh i uh didn't mean
crap she's gonna be pissed
ow sorry about that shito i wasn't paying enough attention
shito it's an emergency what emergency
toka
shito what were you doing just then what do you mean
so after you worried me half to death you came here to make out with her
how dare you
see what i mean you're looking at a rather unstable mental condition
her spirit powers are gradually flowing back into her really what should i do
how rude why didn't you tell me the something that came up was meeting this weird looking little girl
uh no uh she's uh hello there angry lady my name's toka i hate to be the bearer of bad news toka
but it seems as though shito's gotten bored with you
based on what you've already communicated shito stood you up to come here and hang out with me
instead isn't that right i think that's fairly conclusive no what are you talking about
shito you shut your mouth right now i do apologize though being second best is never an easy thing
is it it's because i'm so charming not because there's anything wrong with you toka
but it's not like you can blame shito for blowing you off so he can come play with me
i am pretty adorable
shut up shut up shut up shut up shut up shut up this can't be happening again you can scream all
you want but you're about to hear the brutal truth go on shito tell this poor thing she's not
wanted anymore i am too wanted you you don't know shito was the one who said it was okay
for me to stay here with him why are you lying to me and being so mean i won't take it anymore
say something come on why are you talking now speak what's wrong it won't talk make it talk i was
trying to talk give it back please what are you doing in there the hermit's mental condition is all
over the place too they need to calm down hey so listen toka could you maybe give that back to her
maybe she know she was right you really do like her better than me no it's not that at all
uh what's that
oh no she's releasing her angel this is bad we have to get out of there now her angel did you forget
she took a sandal bun
watch out
you lost her
everyone return to base
you okay toka you're not hurt i'm all right will you just get away but why don't touch me
you like that little girl better than me i know you do admit it wait what that's perfect
looks like someone's got trouble in paradise
you
It's a long way
また会えますか 信じてくれますか 恋に似てひらるもので センサーは
世界が終わる前に生きる大きい 君が笑ってくれたら嬉しいのです
ご視聴ありがとうございました